# **Haein Kim**

hayni100@gmail.com | 923 NE ELIIS DR, ISSAQUAH, WA, 98209 | 443-953-1115

## **Summary**

While working as a healthcare provider at major hospitals in Seattle, I saw great potential in using technology to improve healthcare access and outcomes for underserved communities. Whether it's building a platform to connect patients with healthcare providers, developing a mobile app to promote health literacy, or conducting research to better understand the social determinants of health, I am committed to making a positive impact in the world through my work.

### **Education**

# University of Washington - Professional & Continuing Education 2023

**Graduated March** 

Full-Stack Coding Bootcamp Certification in Web Development

Course highlights: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, jQuery, Moment.js, MySQL database, Node.js, Object Oriented Programming, express.js, Object Relational Mapping, MERN, react, and more

#### **University of Washington - Seattle**

**Graduated May 2022** 

B.A. in Anthropology: Medical Anthropology and Global Health

Course highlights: Microbiology, Organic Chemistry, Behaviors and Hormones, Fundamentals of Psychological Research, Intro to Communication, Intro to Logic, Calculus, Science Evidence and Health

### **Bellevue College - Bellevue**

Course highlights: Intro to Psychology, Lifespan growth and development, Pre-calculus, Nutrition

• Member of Bellevue College Dance Company

### **Work Experience**

### Seattle Children's Hospital - Seattle

October 2021 - June 2022

Oncology Unit Certified Nursing Assistant

- Practice effective and detailed patient charting using EPIC
- Effectively communicating with both the patient and caregivers to optimize comfort for both
- Coordinating patient care with RNs for daily hygiene and activities
- Monitoring supplies and restocking needed items around the unit and reporting damaged, broken items to engineering department

### Virginia Mason Franciscan Health - Seattle

**January 2021 - March 2022** 

Observation and Emergency Unit Certified Nursing Assistant

- Strong foundation in learning and using CERNER for patient charting
- Created a new department filing system by analyzing usage and preferences of the staff and providers in the unit.
- Took on leadership role to train and educate new CNAs in unit
- Performing independent tasks such as obtaining vital signs, collecting biospecimens, operating EKG machines, pre-operational preparation, and blood glucose monitoring

### **Sunrise Dental - Monroe**

May 2020 - February 2021

Certified Dental Assistant/Care coordinator

- Navigated through complex insurance system to verify and organize patient information
- Responsible for appointment scheduling, billing, and coordination with patient's insurance
- Maintaining good relationships and building trust with patients of all ages by effectively communicating and responding to their concerns and comments with respect and empathy
- Assist dental providers in various treatments including oral surgery

### **Volunteering**

### Korean Presbyterian Church - Salisbury

August 2017

Mission trip to Managua, Nicaragua

- Raised funds for a week-long trip to Managua by preparing and selling snacks and goodies for church members
- Promoted personal health by sanitizing homes, providing kids with donated hygiene supplies and educating them on their proper use
- Lead a team of 12 members that was assembled to facilitate a summer camp for over 100 elementary school kids
- Coordinated activities such as arts and crafts, and devised educational plans using Microsoft Suite

Language: Korean - Fluent